question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed&quot;, the player can only drive cars manufactured by Porsche.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals", "question": "Rabbits can&#039;t vomit.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
     "question": "There is a Donald Trump Board Game, which was made in 1989.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Sports",
     "question": "Peyton Manning retired after winning Super Bowl XLIX.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In the Super Mario series, the character Pauline is a Princess like Princess Peach.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Heroes of the Storm, the Cursed Hollow map gimmick requires players to kill the undead to curse the enemy team.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
